http://www.bcot.ac.uk/information/privacy-and-cookies/

Bordon Future Skills Centre: Virtual Open Event
Join us online for the FSC Virtual Open Event to explore everything the Future Skills Centre (FSC) has to offer.
Bordon Future Skills Centre: Virtual Open Event
Join us online for the FSC Virtual Open Event to explore everything the Future Skills Centre (FSC) has to offer.
Term Dates
Why study a vocational course?
Careers, Progression and Industry Placement
Parents Information
Coronavirus Information
Bordon Future Skills Centre: Virtual Open Event
Join us online for the FSC Virtual Open Event to explore everything the Future Skills Centre (FSC) has to offer.
Bordon Future Skills Centre: Virtual Open Event
Join us online for the FSC Virtual Open Event to explore everything the Future Skills Centre (FSC) has to offer.
Privacy and Cookies
Data ProtectionUnder the Data Protection Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you.
Information you provide on the application / enrolment form will be passed to The Education & Skills Funding Agency, which is registered under the Data Protection Act 2018. The registration is primarily for the collection and analysis of statistical data but it also allows the Council to share information with other organisations for the purposes of detecting fraud. Further information about data confidentiality is available upon request from the Data Protection Officer (gdpr@bcot.ac.uk) or from the GDPR page.Privacy NoticeHow We Use Your Personal Information
The personal information you provide for enrolment is passed to the Chief Executive of Skills Funding ("the Agency") and, when needed, the Department for Education, including the Education Funding Agency to meet legal responsibilities under the Apprenticeships, Skills Children and Learning Act 2009, and for the Agency's Learning Records Service (LRS) to create and maintain a unique learner number (ULN). The information you provide may be shared with other organisations for education, training and employment-related purposes, including for research.
Further information and our privacy notices can be found on our GDPR page.
Further information about use of and access to your personal data, and details of organisations with whom we regularly share data are available at:
ESFA: https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/esfa-privacy-notice
LRS: https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/lrs-privacy-notices/lrs-privacy-noticeWhat information do we collect?We collect three kinds of information from visitors to the BCoT website: feedback (through visitors emailing us), requests for course information / prospectus (online forms) and site usage information, from cookies and log files.Site usage informationCookies
Cookies are pieces of data that are often created when you visit a website, and which are stored in the cookie directory of your computer. The BCoT website currently uses cookies to identify you and helps to find specific content for you.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies. If you do not know how to do this, contact us, giving details on the type of browser you are using, and we will do our best to help.
For more information on cookies click here.
Remarketing
We use third-party vendor remarketing tracking cookies, including Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise BCoT across the Internet. Google AdWords Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the BCoT website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. The cookie is used to say: "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google Adwords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. We respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of these third-party vendors.
You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out page and you can opt out of other third-party vendor use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-out page.
Log files
Log files allow us to record visitors' use of the site. We analyse our log files to help us improve your experience, find any dead links and try to correct them.
Log files do not contain any personal information and they are not used to identify any individual patterns of use of the site.
This privacy policy applies only to our site, so you should always be aware when you are moving to another site and read the privacy statement of any site which collects personal information.
We do not pass on any personal information you have given us to any other site.
Google Analytics
We may collect information about your computer, including an anonymised version of your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. The only cookies in use on our site for visitors are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site. Click here to find out how to opt out.Access to your information and contacting BCoTIf you wish to see our records of any correspondence you have sent to us, or if you have a query or complaint about this privacy policy or about the site, you can contact us by email on gdpr@bcot.ac.uk.Changes to this privacy policyIf this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.
See also our GDPR page.Freedom of InformationBCoT has adopted the model publication scheme developed for the Further Education sector and is therefore committed to publishing the information it describes. See scheme for charges, contact details etc.
Download the BCoT Publication Scheme
We welcome your feedback.
If you send an email or letter to us, asking for information, we may need to contact other departments to find that information.
We do not pass on any of your personal information when dealing with your enquiry, unless you have given us permission to do so.
